doctoroogle.com 2018-10-01

# DR.Oogle: Privacy Policy

**PRIVACY POLICY**

Last Modified Nov 23, 2017. 

**Introduction**

DR.Oogle ("us," "we," or "DR.Oogle") is committed to respecting the privacy rights of its customers, visitors, and other users of the DR.Oogle website, located at https://www.doctor-oogle.com and the associated services we provide (the “Services”). We created this Privacy Policy ("Privacy Policy") to give you confidence as you visit and use the Services, and to demonstrate our commitment to fair information practices and the protection of privacy. 

This Privacy Policy is only applicable to the Services, and not to any other websites or services that you may be able to access from the Services, each of which may have data collection, storage, and use practices and policies that differ materially from this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with the practices explained in this Privacy Policy, you should not use our Services. By using our Services, you agree to accept the practices and terms set forth in this Privacy Policy. 

Capitalized terms not defined in this Privacy Policy are defined in the Terms of Service located at  https://www.doctor-oogle.com/legal_terms/. 

**Types of Information Collected**

_Traffic Data_

We may automatically track and collect the following categories of information when you use our Services: (1) IP addresses; (2) domain servers; (3) types of computers accessing the Services; (4) types of web browsers used to access the Services; (5) other information associated with the interaction of your browser and the Services (collectively "Traffic Data"). Traffic Data is anonymous information that does not personally identify you. 

_Personal Information_

In order for you to access certain areas of the Services, we may require you to provide us with certain information that personally identifies you ("Personal Information"). Personal Information includes the following categories of information: (1) Contact Data, such as your e-mail address and DR.Oogle password, and including information made available through an SNS Account as described below; and (2) Demographic Data (such as your zip code, age, and income). If you communicate with us by, for example, e-mail or letter, any information provided in such communication may be collected as Personal Information. 

_Social Network Accounts_

You can also register with our Services and create a Services account by linking your Services acount to your account certain third-party social services such as Facebook (each such account, an “SNS Account”), if and when such functionality is available. If you choose to create a Service account through one of your SNS Accounts, you may have to provide us with your username (or userID) so that your identity can be authenticated by the SNS Account. When the authentication is complete, we’ll be able to link your Services account with the SNS Account. That linking may allow us to access certain Personal Information, such as your name and email address, and other personally identifiable information Depending on the SNS Accounts you choose and subject to applicable SNS privacy settings, personally (e.g., information about your contacts on the social networking service) may be available on and through your DR.Oogle Account. that your privacy settings on the SNS Account permit us to access, in connection with creating your Service account. We don’t receive or store passwords for any of your SNS Accounts. 

_Public Information_

The User Content that you contribute through the Service is intended for public consumption, including your posts, photos, comments, friend list, and any elements of your Account you make visible (e.g., your user name). We may display this information through the Service, share it with businesses, and further distribute it to a wider audience through third party sites and services. 

_User Choice_

You may choose not to provide us with any Personal Information. In such an event, you can still access and use much of the Services; however you will not be able to access and use those portions of the Services that require your Personal Information. 

_Retention_

We will retain your personally identifiable information that we process for as long as needed to provide Services to you, and thereafter as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements. We will retain non-personally-identifiable information such as Demographic Data, Traffic Data and other usage data for as long as we believe it to be useful in our business. 

**Uses of Information Collected**

_By DR.Oogle Itself_

We use the information we collect to market, operate and improve our Services, track the usage of the Services, provide feedback to Providers participating in the Services, display relevant advertising, and comply with legal obligations. Without limiting the generality of the above: (a) we use Contact Data to send you information about DR.Oogle or our products or services, or to contact you when necessary; and (b) we may use your Demographic Data or your Traffic Data to customize and tailor your experience on the Services, displaying content that we think you might be interested in and according to your preferences, and to provide relevant advertising to you. 

_Information Sharing_

We share certain categories of information we collect from you in the ways described in this Privacy Policy. We may share Demographic Data and Traffic Data with advertisers and other third parties only on an aggregate (i.e., non-personally-identifiable) basis. We also share Personal Information and Traffic Data with our business partners who assist us by performing core services (such as hosting, billing, fulfillment, or data storage and security) related to our operation of the Services. Those business partners have all agreed to uphold the same standards of security and confidentiality that we have promised to you in this Privacy Policy, and they will only use your Contact Data and other Personal Information to carry out their specific business obligations to DR.Oogle. Last, we may transfer information about you if DR.Oogle is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, we will use reasonable efforts to notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy. Finally, we may share or release information in the circumstances described below under “Expectations of Privacy”. 

**Cookies and Other Tracking Tools**

_Cookies_

A "cookie" is an element of data that a website, when visited by a user, sends to that user's browser which, in turn, may store that element on the user's hard drive or memory. We use "cookies" to customize your experience of our Services, to improve the security of the Services, to store your password so you do not have to re-enter it each time you visit the Services, and to compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. At your option, expense and responsibility, you may block our cookies or delete our cookies from your hard drive. However, by disabling cookies, you may not have access to the entire set of features of the Services. 

_Other Analytics_

We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. Presently, the only third-party analytics service provider we use is Google Analytics. For Google’s privacy practices see [ this. ](http://www.google.com/analytics/learn/privacy.html) To opt out of data recording and analysis by Google Analytics, see [ this. ](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout)

_Do Not Track_

We use only cookies as described above. We do not use cookies to collect personally identifiable information or track users’ online activities over time and across different web sites. For information regarding Do Not Track mechanisms, see <http://allaboutdnt.com/>. 

**Expectations of Privacy**

Except as otherwise provided in this Privacy Policy, we will keep your Personal Information private and will not share it with third parties, unless we believe in good faith that disclosure of your Personal Information or any other information we collect about you is appropriate to: (a) comply with the law, or a law enforcement agency request, subpoena, court order or other such request by a legal authority; (b) protect the rights, property or personal safety of DR.Oogle or anyone else; (c) enforce our Terms and policies, to otherwise establish or exercise our rights, or defend against legal claims; (d) investigate, prevent and take action regarding fraud or misuse of the Service or (d) respond to claims that any posting or other content violates the rights of third parties. 

_Providers_

**Providers, their employees, and their agents should be particularly aware of their obligations of patient confidentiality, including without limitation their obligations under HIPAA, both in communicating with DR.Oogle or other Users, posting User Content and in responding to postings and comments.** **DR.Oogle does not have and will not accept any obligations of confidentiality with respect to any communications other than those expressly stated in this Privacy Policy and the DR.Oogle Terms of Service.**

_Public Information_

**Any information that you may reveal in a posting or other online discussion or forum is intentionally open to the public and is not in any way confidential or private. You should think carefully before disclosing any personally identifiable information in any public forum. What you have written may be seen and/or collected by third parties and may be used by others in ways we are unable to control or predict.**

**Reasonable Efforts**

Although we make good faith efforts to store Personal Information in a secure operating environment that is not open to the public, you should guarantee that there will be no unintended disclosures of your Personal Information. If we become aware that your Personal Information has been disclosed in a manner not in accordance with this Privacy Policy, we will use reasonable efforts to notify you of the nature and extent of the disclosure (to the extent we know that information), as soon as reasonably possible and as permitted by law. 

We will use reasonable efforts to comply with this Privacy Policy and to take prompt corrective action when we learn of any failure to comply with our Privacy Policy. We sometimes release beta versions of our products and services, which are further refined before the release of the final version. Because these products and services are still in a test phase, we may not always catch an unintended privacy issue, despite our efforts to do so. As such, we welcome feedback on any privacy concerns. In light of the above and because of the complex and constantly changing nature of our technology and business, and the security risks associated with using the Internet, we do not guarantee error-free performance under this Privacy Policy. TO THE EXTENT PERMISSIBLE UNDER LAW, SMILINGDOCS SHALL NOT BE LIABLE FOR ANY INCIDENTAL, CONSEQUENTIAL OR PUNITIVE DAMAGES RELATING TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY. 

**Inquiries**

Upon request, we will provide you with information about whether we hold, or process on behalf of a third party, any of your personally identifiable information. To request this information please contact us at the address at the end of this Privacy Policy. If your personal information changes, or if you no longer desire to use the Services, you may correct, update, amend, delete/remove, or deactivate it by contacting us at the addresses at the end of this Privacy Policy. Before we process any request, we may request personal information to verify your identity where allowed by law. Where permitted by local law, we may reject requests that are unreasonable or impractical. We will respond to your request within a reasonable time frame. 

**International Transfer**

Your Personal Information may be transferred to, and maintained on, computers located outside of your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the privacy laws may not be as protective as those in your jurisdiction. If you’re located outside the United States and choose to provide your personally identifiable information to us, we may transfer your personally identifiable information to the United States and process it there. 

**Updates and Changes**

We reserve the right, at any time and without advance notice, to add to, change, update, or modify this Privacy Policy, simply by posting such change, update, or modification on the Services and without any other notice to you. If you have established an Account for the Services, we will attempt to inform you of any modifications to this Privacy Policy that affect your obligations to us or our obligations to you: (a) by a message displayed at the time you log into the Services, and / or (b) by such other means as we deem reasonably likely to reach you. If you do not agree with any such modifications, the sole remedy is the termination of your Account. Your continued use of the Services after receiving notice of any modifications indicates your acceptance of the modified Privacy Policy. 

If you have not established an account for the Services, any modifications to this Privacy Policy will be effective upon our posting of the new terms and/or upon implementation of the new changes on the Services, and your continued use of the Services after any modifications indicates acceptance of the modified Privacy Policy. You agree to review this Privacy Policy periodically so that you are aware of any modifications. 

**Contacting Us**

If you have any comments on or questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact: 

DR.Oogle Inc   
PO BOX 1107   
Palo Alto, CA 94302   
Email contact 

Copyright 2017, DR.Oogle Inc.
